[Music] It has
happened
[Music]
Hello friends welcome to Option Gyan channel
friends today we are going to discuss this
topic for you that this is lock stock
and current all friends you have to
click on continue this stock
you have to share it around 9491 it
falls below next to friends
so you people who are around then have to wish that
you people will finally do Bigg Boss of
this stock friends you will do it at 397 that is
you people have to invest
only
30% capital in this stock right now that is your 30% capital will be
invested
around 491
and the remaining 30% capital of yours will be invested
around 454 and the remaining
40% of yours will be invested at
397 friends again some people will
feel that this stoploss is far but
friends if you are connected to my videos
then you people must not have seen till now
that the stock has reached the previous level or has gone down from next to then there will be a
very good profit in that till now
friends the stocks that I have given
I was adding to it, so why write
Wimp, last friends, who went on the development of his PC
and today it also came around 545, from
there a lot of pack marketing, very good
returns are being received from that too,
so
I am telling you guys that it is
very important to save your wicket by doing Pulsar market, you
guys also have to do money management, you
also have to see that if I am buying this stock, then
if it goes down,
how much profit will it make by wishing, so that if there is
that movement towards the top, then I can
quickly come within my profit, so
all these things will be right for you guys, you
guys should do capital management, friends,
money is not made just by buying shares,
you guys know that if you buy a stock and do
not do fables on it, then it can take
time to reach there, even if it comes now,
you guys will be very scared that you come today, it has come, get out, it has
come after a long time, so many such
things come in the mind
that those who do it, they must have known that everything must have been done by
pressing,
but if you people do this method  If you work with it
then definitely you guys must be having fun
with me friends that
why I prefer this stock
friends because if this stock
crosses 1500 then it is
preparing to have breakfast and till now it
continues at a lifetime high speed then if it reaches ₹500
then very soon you guys will get 534 in it
and these are large cap stocks, if I
discuss the fundamentals of the company with you then
you guys will see
why the stock is being considered low in it
friends, mutual fund fi di should
increase its building and will be editing in it, the
company has a
lot of shares in it, they have
also been released, so they will also see, so
if the stock crosses 500 then
very quickly a target of 534 will be achieved, the
position attendants will edit around 500 34540
but those who want to
invest in it should go for it and
whenever the stock is available in the depot then keep liking
until there is a negative bias
Yadav, if any negative energy comes then I will
update it on my channel. Now let's
discuss its fundamentals on
paper only. Friends,
if we talk about the company's pencil stand, then
you must be seeing the company's profit increasing every year
and the company has achieved the highest revenue till date when you compare from 2018 to 2021 on paper
and the company still has six more months to
work. Talking about the net profit of the company,
friends, the profit of the company is going to almost
double
in Twenty20
and if you check the financial statement level, then
you will see that the best is
looking better than the best.
Friends,
where the industry review guru nine
FH, there the profit of this company is
21.62 percent, that is, almost more than double
and the company has
doubled its profit in 5 years, sure friends, where the
question of the company is
more,
if the industry because friends,
sure, but the net profit of this company
People must be seeing the profit of 2% as excellent and
now let's
see the promoter holding,
that too will appear excellent to you.
Next, let's talk about promoter holding,
friends, of course you people are getting surrounded, so the
company which had made the pledge, these
people are looking different, the company had made the pledge,
so see, that pledge part has become Bigg
Boss free, almost 1 is a
very good part for the company, friends, friends,
mutual funds, friends,
increase your position in every quarter, make a
tremendous increase even in the DIG range,
friends,
how did you increase your position very forcefully,
but FIR Navy friends, increase your holding in
this stock, then why are you people
behind, you people also fix the stock at around
1.5 crore 500, then if you
look at the position, very soon you will see the target of 500 34540
and if you people
want to invest in it and
want to save, then also it is a good stock of Aastha,
so you people must have liked this video
and it will be very beneficial for you, friends,
if you people like my video  If you are getting benefit
then please share it. Share this video with your
friends, your relatives and anyone who
wants to earn in the stock market.
I hope you
liked this video. With this hope,
friends, I end this video.
Thank you. So
friends, if you liked this video, then
please do not forget to like, share and subscribe.
Thank you for watching my video.
[Music]